keystonebankng.com 2013-12-04

# 

Thank you for visiting us online at [www.keystonebankng.com](http://www.keystonebankng.com/). At Keystone Bank, we strive to do everything we can to respect the trust Customers have in our brand, and our commitment to your privacy is no exception. We are committed to protecting and safeguarding Customer and user privacy on the Internet. 

Thanks again for visiting our web site and for placing your trust in Keystone Bank Plc.  
 **  
Keystone Bank INTERNET PRIVACY POLICY**

Keystone Bank is pleased to provide information to all of our Customers about our online privacy policy. Please be assured that Keystone Bank uses its best efforts to protect the privacy of visitors to this web site. 

**TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW IT IS USED**

Keystone Bank only gathers personal information, such as, first and last names, addresses and email addresses, when voluntarily submitted by you. For example, personal information may be collected from you in order to contact you with further information on our Bank, our website and our products.

 **SHARING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION**

Companies may be engaged by Keystone Bank to perform a variety of functions, such as, providing technical services for our web sites, etc. These companies may have access to personal information if needed to perform such functions. However, these companies may only use such personal information for the purpose of performing that function and may not use it for any other purpose. 

Keystone Bank does not sell, transfer or disclose personal information to third parties. Occasionally, with your permission, we will send marketing information to you, such as information about new product offerings, etc. If you do not elect to receive such materials, we will not send them to you. 

Keystone Bank reserves the right to use or disclose any information as needed to satisfy any law, regulation or legal request, to protect the integrity of the site, to fulfill your requests, or to cooperate in any law enforcement investigation or an investigation on a matter of public safety. 

**ACCESS TO OUR WEBSITE**

You are not required to register to use Keystone Bank’s website. You are in control of any personal information you provide to us on-line. If at any time, you would like to correct the personal information we have about you, you can let us know by contacting us at the email or postal address listed below. 

**COOKIES**

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow the website to remember information about your use of the site. Unlike most websites, Keystone Bank does not use cookies because we believe in protecting your privacy by granting unreservedly your right to anonymity

 **CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY**

This privacy policy is effective as of April 26, 2006. From time to time, it may be necessary for Keystone Bank to change this privacy policy. If we change our policy, we will post the revised version here, so we suggest that you check here periodically for the most up-to-date version of our privacy policy. Rest assured, however, that any changes will not be retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information.

 **HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about our Keystone Bank Internet Privacy Policy, please contact us at: 

Corporate Communications Division  
Keystone Bank Limited,  
1 Keystone Bank Crescent,  
Victoria Island, Lagos, Nigeria  
Tel: 234 70 8060 5000, +234 448 5742  
or e-mail us at [customercare@keystonebankng.com](mailto:customercare@keystonebankng.com)
